<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>C# on Soumya Thakur | Game Developer</title>
    <link>https://soummy21.github.io/portfolio/tags/c#/</link>
    <description>Recent content in C# on Soumya Thakur | Game Developer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://soummy21.github.io/portfolio/tags/c#/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gorilla Chase</title>
      <link>https://soummy21.github.io/portfolio/professional/gorilla_chase/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soummy21.github.io/portfolio/professional/gorilla_chase/</guid>
      <description>About the game! With over 200K+ downloads and consistently in the Top 50 (Action), Gorilla Chase is a game of tag with a twist where either you need to survive an onslaught of angry gorillas or tag as many as you can!
My Contribution Role : Game Programmer | Game Designer Implemented the entire backend architechture for the game. The architecture was event and state driven in nature. Built all the gameplay interaction and base AI systems as well scripted the animations for the UI system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Towers Of Hell: Challenge</title>
      <link>https://soummy21.github.io/portfolio/professional/toh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soummy21.github.io/portfolio/professional/toh/</guid>
      <description>About the game! Towers of Hell is a 3D platformer game which challenges players to climb towers of varying difficulty while going through traps and unlocking new perks. The towers are unrelenting so be careful and try your best!
My Contribution Role : Game Programmer | Game Designer Implemented the entire backend architechture for the game. The architecture was event and state driven in nature. Built a modified third person controller and input system for smooth controls on any mobile even lower end ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scared of Heights</title>
      <link>https://soummy21.github.io/portfolio/professional/soh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soummy21.github.io/portfolio/professional/soh/</guid>
      <description>About the game! Scared of Heights? Well, overcome it; because in this hyper-casual game you need to race to the finish line while flipping above high mountains and terrains as well as dodging trees, rocks and anything nature throws at you!
My Contribution Role : Game Programmer Built the prototype input controls as well movement mechanics (running and flying) which was used as the backbone for improvements. Hooked consumable and subscription based in-app-purchases using the UnityIAP API.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
